[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Which action best describes a MAC address spoofing attack?",
    "choices": [
      "altering the MAC address of an attacking host to match that of a legitimate host",
      "bombarding a switch with fake source MAC addresses",
      "forcing the election of a rogue root bridge",
      "flooding the LAN with excessive traffic"
    ],
    "answer": 0,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "4.4.2 Attacking What We Do Quiz"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is an objective of a DHCP spoofing attack?",
    "choices": [
      "to gain illegal access to a DHCP server and modify its configuration",
      "to attack a DHCP server and make it unable to provide valid IP addresses to DHCP clients",
      "to intercept DHCP messages and alter the information before sending to DHCP clients",
      "to provide false DNS server addresses to DHCP clients so that visits to a legitimate web server are directed to a fake server"
    ],
    "answer": 3,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "4.4.2 Attacking What We Do Quiz"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the primary means for mitigating virus and Trojan horse attacks?",
    "choices": [
      "antivirus software",
      "encryption",
      "antisniffer software",
      "blocking ICMP echo and echo-replies"
    ],
    "answer": 0,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "4.4.2 Attacking What We Do Quiz"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What method can be used to mitigate ping sweeps?",
    "choices": [
      "blocking ICMP echo and echo-replies at the network edge",
      "deploying antisniffer software on all network devices",
      "using encrypted or hashed authentication protocols",
      "installing antivirus software on hosts"
    ],
    "answer": 0,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "4.4.2 Attacking What We Do Quiz"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What worm mitigation phase involves actively disinfecting infected systems?",
    "choices": [
      "quarantine",
      "inoculation",
      "treatment",
      "containment"
    ],
    "answer": 2,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "4.4.2 Attacking What We Do Quiz"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is the result of a DHCP starvation attack?",
    "choices": [
      "Legitimate clients are unable to lease IP addresses.",
      "Clients receive IP address assignments from a rogue DHCP server.",
      "The attacker provides incorrect DNS and default gateway information to clients.",
      "The IP addresses assigned to legitimate clients are hijacked."
    ],
    "answer": 0,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "4.4.2 Attacking What We Do Quiz"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which term is used for bulk advertising emails flooded to as many end users as possible?",
    "choices": [
      "Phishing",
      "Brute force",
      "Spam",
      "Adware"
    ],
    "answer": 2,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "4.4.2 Attacking What We Do Quiz"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which type of DNS attack involves the cybercriminal compromising a parent domain and creating multiple subdomains to be used during the attacks?",
    "choices": [
      "cache poisoning",
      "amplification and reflection",
      "tunneling",
      "shadowing"
    ],
    "answer": 3,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "4.4.2 Attacking What We Do Quiz"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which protocol would be the target of a cushioning attack?",
    "choices": [
      "DNS",
      "HTTP",
      "ARP",
      "DHCP"
    ],
    "answer": 1,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "4.4.2 Attacking What We Do Quiz"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which language is used to query a relational database?",
    "choices": [
      "Python",
      "C++",
      "Java",
      "SQL"
    ],
    "answer": 3,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "4.4.2 Attacking What We Do Quiz"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Which two attacks target web servers through exploiting possible vulnerabilities of input functions used by an application? (Choose two.)",
    "choices": [
      "SQL injection",
      "port scanning",
      "port redirection",
      "trust exploitation",
      "cross-site scripting"
    ],
    "answer": [0, 4],
    "type": "multiple-choice-v2",
    "category": "4.4.2 Attacking What We Do Quiz"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "In which type of attack is falsified information used to redirect users to malicious Internet sites?",
    "choices": [
      "DNS cache poisoning",
      "ARP cache poisoning",
      "DNS amplification and reflection",
      "domain generation"
    ],
    "answer": 0,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "4.4.2 Attacking What We Do Quiz"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What is a characteristic of a DNS amplification and reflection attack?",
    "choices": [
      "Threat actors use DNS open resolvers to increase the volume of attacks and to hide the true source of an attack.",
      "Threat actors use a DoS attack that consumes the resources of the DNS open resolvers.",
      "Threat actors hide their phishing and malware delivery sites behind a quickly-changing network of compromised DNS hosts.",
      "Threat actors use malware to randomly generate domain names to act as rendezvous points."
    ],
    "answer": 0,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "4.4.2 Attacking What We Do Quiz"
  }
]
